<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AAR UoS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="direction_api_address">https://maps.googleapis.com/maps/api/directions/</string>
    <string name="welcome_op">Welcome, freshman. I am your guide. Today I will lead you to experience a day as an ECS MSc student.</string>
    <string name="click_to_go">Now, press the button below to start our journey!</string>
    <string name="interchange_op">Hi, freshman! Let\'s go to the Interchange first. Interchange is the transportation center of Southampton University. Almost all UniLink buses stop here. These buses will take you to any place in Southampton.</string>
    <string name="interchange_ed">Now we are arriving at the University Interchange. Remember, you can use your unlink card to take the bus of any route start with U.
            And the routes end with C are usually go to the city centre.</string>
    <string name="building_53_op">OK, let\'s go to the Building 53 to see your mentor, who is usually a PhD student and will help you in the future.</string>
    <string name="building_53_ed">Great, we are in Building 53 now. It is also called Mountbatten Building which is named after a school leader of ECS.
        Freshman, I think you have to attend your Software Modelling class now! Go to the building 58 now! It is just near the Building 53!
    </string>
    <string name="building_58_op">Hum, we are just on time! Listen, Building 58 is also called Murray Building, it is where Mathematics School located in.
            As a ECS student, sometimes you have lectures in the building belongs to another school.</string>
    <string name="building_58_ed">Hey, it is 12 o\'clock now, let\'s go to have lunch! And your tutor is waiting you in the Library.
            What\'s more don\'t forget to go to the SUSU shop to buy some notebooks.
           Where do you want to go first?</string>
    <string name="restaurant_op">Great! Let\'s go to the piazza restaurant to enjoy half chicken meal! It\'s in Building 42, I will lead you there!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_ed">Here we are at restaurant, you can enjoy any food you like here! Let\'s just finish the lunch and go to the next point!</string>
    <string name="library_op">OK! Go to the Hartley Library it\'s building 36. And you may need to cross the road.
        Be careful to watch the traffic lights when crossing the road.</string>
    <string name="library_ed">Go! your tutor is sitting in the cafe! See you later! And let\'s go to the next point!</string>
    <string name="shop_op">SUSU shop is a good choice to save money! It\'s in Building 57，Let\'s go!</string>
    <string name="shop_ed">Here we are in SUSU shop! I think you can have a job here if you want to work in the university. OK, let\'s go to the next point!</string>
    <string name="eee_op">Do you know you will have a MSc project this year? Go to the Building 32 to meet your supervisor Dave in room 3031!</string>
    <string name="eee_ed">I think you can do well in your MSc project!
            However, if you want to do your project well, I think you can start learning from now! Now, let\'s do it!
            You can just go to the building 16 nearby, it is the ECS lab for MSc students, you can also go to the hartley library.
            Or you can go to the Zepler Building Lab. It is just near the Mountbatten Building! So which do you prefer?</string>
    <string name="loc1_op">OK, just do it!</string>
    <string name="loc1_ed">Are you sure you have finished? Come on! If you don\'t like it, we can go to another place!</string>
    <string name="loc2_op">It\'s great that you are happy with this place!</string>
    <string name="loc2_ed">Great! You work so hard! Let\'s go to the Jubilee Sports Centre to have fun. It\'s Building 18, just near the SUSU Shop!</string>
    <string name="sports_op">The Jubilee Sports Centre on Highfield Campus is a state-of-the-art £8.5 million complex, boasting an array of high quality facilities.
        The centre is complemented by further indoor facilities in the nearby Student\'s Union building</string>
    <string name="sports_ed">Here we are at Jubilee Sports Hall! You can see the swimming pool, and there is also a gym and indoor basketball court.</string>
    <string name="end_op">That\'s all about today, freshman! Go to the interchange and catch a bus, see you tomorrow!</string>
    <string name="end_ed">Thank you for using!</string>
    <string name="end_slogan">Thank you!\nEnjoy your University life!</string>
</resources>
